const questionData = [
    {
        question: "Who is Ororo Munroe?",
        A: "Rogue",
        B: "Psylocke",
        C: "Storm",
        D: "Jubilee",
        correctAnswer: "Storm"
    },
    {
        question: "Who did Rogue first kiss?",
        A: "Gambit",
        B: "David",
        C: "Iceman",
        D: "Cody",
        correctAnswer: "Cody"
    },
    {
        question: "Who does Cyclops first marry?",
        A: "Madelyne Pryor",
        B: "Jean Grey",
        C: "Rogue",
        D: "Storm",
        correctAnswer: "Madelyne Pryor"
    },
    {
        question: "Before the X-Men, what group was Gambit apart of?",
        A: "X-Force",
        B: "Thieves' Guild",
        C: "Rogue's Guild",
        D: "X-Factor",
        correctAnswer: "Thieves' Guild"
    },
    {
        question: "What X-Men looked up to Wolverine?",
        A: "Rogue",
        B: "Kitty Pryde",
        C: "Jubilee",
        D: "X-23",
        correctAnswer: "Jubilee"
    },
    {
        question: "Before becoming Phoenix, what was Jean Grey's alias?",
        A: "Marvel Girl",
        B: "Ms. Marvel",
        C: "Captain Marvel",
        D: "Mar'vel",
        correctAnswer: "Marvel Girl"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Charles Xavier's brother?",
        A: "Juggernaut",
        B: "Shadow King",
        C: "Magneto",
        D: "Banshee",
        correctAnswer: "Juggernaut"
    },
    {
        question: "what is Beast's real name?",
        A: "Henry 'Hank' McCoy",
        B: "Kurt Wagner",
        C: "Erik 'Joseph' Lehnsherr",
        D: "Remy LeBeau",
        correctAnswer: "Henry 'Hank' McCoy"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Nightcrawler's father?",
        A: "Dr. Strange",
        B: "Arnos",
        C: "Azazel",
        D: "Stefan",
        correctAnswer: "Azazel"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Nightcrawler's mother?",
        A: "Jardine",
        B: "Magik",
        C: "Margali",
        D: "Mystique",
        correctAnswer: "Mystique"
    },
]

const correctResults = [
    {
        statement: "Congratulations! You knocked Rogue down!",
        image: "https://i.makeagif.com/media/10-06-2015/lyuTeh.gif",
        alt: "Rogue falls down"
    },
    {
        statement: "Congratulations! You threw Rogue far!",
        image: "https://thumbs.gfycat.com/SlipperyPoliteGemsbuck-size_restricted.gif",
        alt: "Rogue is thrown into boulders"
    },
    
]

const wrongResults = [
    {
        statement: "Rogue Knocked you out! Better luck next time.",
        image: "https://68.media.tumblr.com/416eee7b302bd6581976415c68f82cb7/tumblr_o6qzdunFiH1sgixyoo1_500.gif",
        alt: "Rogue punches you"
    },
    {
        statement: "Rogue absorbed your powers. Watch out for her hands!",
        image: "https://media1.tenor.com/images/f89881acd0b30049a29af8bed01846df/tenor.gif?itemid=5056826",
        alt: "Rogue absorbs your powers"
    },
    {
        statement: "Rogue throws you across the room. Thanks Carol...",
        image: "https://thumbs.gfycat.com/BreakableSeparateAtlanticbluetang-size_restricted.gif",
        alt: "Rogue throws you"
    },
]